Back then,
あの時 二人がどんな状況で
I didn't know what was going on,
or what they had talked about.
どんな話をしていたのか
私 全然 分かってなかった
I didn't have any idea.
I didn't even know how I felt.
自分の気持ちすら
分かってなかった
先 輩
Ichika?
あ あのう
Um,
先輩 これは ですね
We were, uh...
わ 私
I... I'm sorry!
ご ごめんなさい
Wait!
先輩
でも 見ているのがすごく嫌で
But I really didn't want to see it.
Takatsuki?
貴月先輩
Back then,
あの時の私は
I was scared of facing...
自分の気持ちと向き合うのが
怖かったのだ
my feelings.
Tetsuro!
哲郎さん
本字幕由诸神字幕组制作，仅供交流学习，禁止用于商业用途
更多中日双语字幕，请登录www.Kamigami.org
日听：秋水无痕 翻译：yaya 校对：小草爱吃梨 Syura 时间轴：小青
もう 照れ屋さんなんだから
He's such a shy guy!
Actually, why am I...
っていうか 私なんで
ここまで来れば もう大丈夫だろう
I think we're far enough away now.
っつか あの子 強引過ぎだって
That girl is way too aggressive.
言わないで
Don't tell anyone!
お願い
Please!
誰にも
言わないで
Don't tell anyone!
な 何を
Tell anyone what?
Tetsuro?
哲郎
Let's head back.
戻ろうぜ
Lemon will get mad at us
早くしないと
檸檬先輩に怒られる
if we take too long.
あの
I want to go back to my room first.
私 部屋に戻って
ああ そっか じゃあ 先に戻ってっから
Oh. Okay, I'll meet you there.
You sure took your sweet time!
やっと戻ってきた
Sorry.
わ 悪い
一体 二人で何してたの
What were you two up to?
Well...
そ それは
He was giving me acting tips.
演技について教えてもらってたんです
海ちゃん 完璧主義だから
Seaboy is such a little perfectionist.
Really?
本当に
Yeah, it wasn't that big of a deal.
ああ まあ ちょっとしたことなんだけどさ
By the way, where is...
それより 先輩は
Sorry, guys! I'm late!
すみません
遅くなりました
That took a while.
遅かったわね
何かあったの
Did something happen?
あ ええ 別に 何も
No, nothing really.
ああ っつか それよりか イチカ先輩は
By the way, where's Ichika?
ここにいるけど
I'm right here.
あれ いつの間に
When did you come back?
あのう 先輩 さっきは
Hey, about what happened...
Let's get back
撮影 始めましょう
to the movie.
よい スタート
And action.
さあ 観念なさい
Give yourself up!
Listen to what I have to say.
は 話を聞いて
あなたは犯罪者なのよ
You're a criminal!
樹下が急に泣き出して
Kinoshita started crying all of a sudden.
If you want me to...
If you want money, I can pay!
She showed up out of the blue,
先輩がいきなり現れて
何も分からないまま
and I just continued filming without making sense of anything.
カメラ回して
A UFO!
UFO
なんか ギクシャクしてるなって
Huh? Where is it?
Everything just felt so awkward.
どこどこ どこにいるの
Over there!
It's right there!
どこ そこ そこにある そこ
このままじゃいけないんじゃないかって 思ったりまして
It probably can't go on like this.
Here's my chance!
隙あり
Please let me go!
お願い 見逃して
Then answer my question!
だったら 私の質問に答えなさい
あなたはどうして この星に来たの そして
Why did you come to this planet? And...
And...
そして
And what's your true goal?
そして 本当の目的を
海ちゃんが好きなの
Do you like Seaboy?
な 何を
What?!
カット
Cut!
ご ごめんなさい
Sorry!
先輩
Something wrong?
Let's film this scene again from a different angle.
今のシーン 角度変えてもう一度行きましょう
Okay! Tanigawa, help me carry this.
はい
谷川 バックお願い
Okay! Mio, we're moving stuff.
美桜 移るよ
Did I surprise you?
脅かせちゃいました
Okay!
はい
Come on, Lemon! Make yourself useful.
檸檬先輩も手伝ってくださいよ
What about you?
あなたはどうなの
I'm communicating with the movie gods right now. They're descending upon me now...
今 まさに 映画の神と交信しているの
海人君の
Kaito is...
待って 哲郎さん
Wait up, Tetsuro!
Huh?
あれ 千春
Chiharu?
アグレッシブだよね
That girl's pretty aggressive.
有沢さんだっけ
What was her name again? Arisawa?
あの子可愛いし
She's cute. Tetsuro should just date her already.
哲郎 付き合っちゃえばいいのに
Don't say that to Tetsuro.
そんなこと 哲郎君に言っちゃダメだよ
なんで
Why not?
どうしても
Just because.
Kitahara.
北原さん
代わりに レフ板持ってくれる
Could you hold up the reflective board for now?
Okay...
わ 分かりました
撮影 続けるわよ
We're going to continue filming.
Oh, okay.
ああ はい
海ちゃん
Seaboy!
可愛く撮ってね
Make sure I look cute, okay?
Yeah, yeah.
イチカ 準備はいい
Ichika, are you ready?
うん 大丈夫
Yeah, I'm fine.
哲郎君
Tetsuro...
This should be far enough.
ここまで来れば
どこまでですか
From what?
哲郎さん
Tetsuro!
哲郎は あのまま 戻ってこないし
Tetsuro never came back.
Mio went off once we were done.
美桜も 終わった途端 いなくなっちゃうし
Takatsuki vanished too.
貴月先輩もいないし
か 海人君いる
Are you in there, Kaito?
失礼します
Excuse me!
あれ いない
Huh? He's not here.
霧島君なら
Kirishima was in a real hurry.
さっき そそくさと出かけて行ったわ
恐らく
I assume he wants to meet Kinoshita.
樹下さんのところね
So Kaito really does like her.
海人君 やっぱり 樹下さんのこと
No, he doesn't.
いいえ それはないわ
What makes you so sure?
なんでそう言い切れるんですか
見ていれば分かるもの
I can tell what he's feeling just by looking at him.
霧島君の気持ち
Just by looking at him?
見ていれば
That's right.
Then could you tell me...
あの よかったら 教えてもらえませんか
...tell me how he feels?
その 気持ちっていうの
Of course.
ええ ゆっくりと語り合いましょう
Let me tell you the whole story.
7035室の樹下様は お出かけになっております
Ms. Kinoshita from Room 703 is presently away.
I see...
えっ そうですか
霧島様でいらっしゃいますよね
You are Mr. Kirishima, I assume?
樹下様から 伝言をお預かりしております
Ms. Kinoshita left a message for you.
I see...
遅かったですね
You took your time.
待ってください 哲郎さん
Wait up, Tetsuro!
How much longer is she gonna chase me?
つうか 何時間走らせるんだよ 鉄人か あの子は
Is she a robot or what?
Wait for me!
まってください
Tetsuro!
哲郎君
Mio?
美桜
哲郎君
Tetsuro!
Don't be so shy! Come on out, Tetsuro!
恥かしがっちゃって 哲郎さん どこですか
また 助けられた
I owe you another one.
ありがとうな 美桜
Thanks, Mio.
I should be the one thanking you.
お礼だよ 黙っててくれた
You're keeping it a secret.
な なんだっけ それ
What are you talking about?
優しいね 哲郎君は
That's so nice of you, Tetsuro.
I guess.
まあな
I only do that for cute girls, though.
可愛い女の子限定だけどな
いや その
Well, I mean...
There you are!
見つけた
Tetsuro, you meanie! Don't run away!
ひどいじゃないですか 哲郎さん
にげまわったりして
But you know, I don't mind the foreplay.
そういうプレーも嫌いじゃないですけど
さ デートの続き 楽しみましょう
Now, let's enjoy the rest of our date!
We were on a date?
い 今まで テートだったの
もちろんです
Of course!
ダメ ダメ
No!
呼び出しておいて 遅れてきて
First you ask me to meet you here, and then you show up late.
しかも 黙りですか
And now you're keeping quiet?
Sorry.
ごめんなさい
I'm having trouble sorting all this out.
うまく 考えがまとまらなくて
あのね ちゃんと 聞いておきたいって思って
I couldn't get my thoughts together.
I wanted to ask you how you really feel... about Kaito.
その 樹下さんは海人君のことを
その どう
I love him.
好きですよ
って言ったら どうします
If I told you that, what would you do?
Is this a game to you?
か からかってるの
Sorry, I'm just a little jealous.
ごめんなさい
ちょっと羨ましくて
振られちゃったんです
I was dumped.
私
What are you doing?
ちょっと 何するのよ
You're bothering Tetsuro...
て 哲郎君が め 迷惑してると思って
And why's that?
なんで 迷惑になるわけ
ねえ 哲郎さん
You tell her, Tetsuro!
I, uh...
いや あのさ
Hey!
ほら
But...
けど
分かった
Oh, I get it! You like Tetsuro, don't you?
あなた 哲郎さんのこと好きなんでしょう
あの そ それは
Well, um, I...
可笑しいんじゃない
Don't you think that's weird?
あんたなんて 露出狂のくせに
You're just some exhibitionist!
ちょ おい
I know what I saw!
私見ちゃったんだから
You had no panties on when you tackled me!
あなたが飛び込んできたとき
下着つけてなかったの
I mean, that's weird, right? Really weird, right?!
それって可笑しいよね
可笑しいでしょう
Admit it!
きっとあれよ
下着も穿かずに 出歩いて
You go commando and enjoy imagining others finding out! You're just a pervert!
誰かに見られること想像して楽しんでる変態さんなんでしょう
そんな女の子に好かれたなんて 哲郎さんは
He wouldn't like it if a girl like you—
That's enough!
I'm a nudist!
裸族です
Huh?
私 ら 裸族なんです
I'm a nudist!
ふ ふら 振られたっていうのは その
You were dumped?
海人君に
By Kaito?
違う 違う
No, by a boy at my school in Tokyo.
東京の学校の先輩に
沖縄に来たのは傷心旅行だったりするんですよ
I came to Okinawa to get away.
I see...
そうだったの
Then I ran into Seaboy again after so many years,
そしたら
偶然 海ちゃんと再会して
and I tried to act happy to distract myself from how lonely I was feeling after being dumped.
はしゃいで 彼氏に振られた寂しい気持ち
紛らわそうとして
I guess I caused some trouble by doing that.
そのことで いっぱい迷惑かけちゃいました
Sorry.
ごめんなさい
No, it's okay.
ううん そんなこと
So that's what's going on.
まあ そういうことなので
Why?
どうして
どうして あの時泣いていたの
Why were you crying back then?
He used the very same words
彼氏に振られた時の言葉をそっくりそのまま
海ちゃんに言われたんです
my boyfriend used to dump me.
それ思い出したら
I couldn't help crying when it all came back.
無性に泣けてきちゃって
あの時 海ちゃん こう言ったんですよ
Let me tell you what Seaboy told me back then.
俺には 好きな人がいるって
He said he has someone he loves.
きっと あなたのことだと思います
I think he meant you.
何を
What are you...
I could tell just by looking at him.
海ちゃん見てれば 分かります
I mean, I have known him since we were little.
これでも 一応幼馴染ですし
And you love him too, don't you?
それに あなただってそうなんでしょう
わ 私は
I...
だから お詫びです
So I wanted to apologize.
えっ 樹下っ
Ki-Kinoshita!
See you tomorrow for the movie!
明日も撮影よろしくです
Apologize?
お詫びって
You're here too?
あれ 先輩
海人君
Kaito?
Kinoshita told me to come here...
俺 樹下に呼ばれて来たんですけど
でも どうして 先輩が
Why are you here?
Uh... hello?
あのう 先輩
分かってた
I knew the whole time.
Knew what?
何が
きっと 分かってたの
I must've always known.
先輩
Come on.
Spill the beans.
そろそろ 教えてくださいよ
Can you tell me how Kaito feels now?
海人君の気持ち
Let's see. If you put this outfit on, I'll think about it.
そうね
この衣装を着てくれれば
考えないでもないわ
What? That again?
ええ またですか
Your Feelings.
Episode Seven
Nudist?
裸族
Nudist as in you walk around the house naked?
えと 裸族って あれ
家の中を全裸でフリーダムで過ごすっていう あれ
Yes.
そうです
That's how my family is, and they raised me that way.
家族もそうで
幼いごろから 私もそうで
I thought everyone did that at home.
うちではそうするんだって思ってて
When I started elementary school, I realized that wasn't true at all.
小学校に入ったあたりから なんだか違うなって思い始めたんですけど
I couldn't tell anyone about this.
こんなこと誰にも言えないし
ええっと
I know you're supposed to wear underwear.
下着をつけるのが当たり前だってこと
わかってます
But my blood pressure is really low.
でも 私 すごい 低血圧なんです
Sometimes in the morning, I just space out and end up going places without any underwear...
朝ボーっとして たまに 下着を穿き 忘れて
そのまま 学校行ったりして
It's really embarrassing.
すごく恥ずかしくて
I know it's wrong for me to be like this,
これじゃ いけないって思って
and I've tried to break the habit, but...
何度も 何度も 直そうとしたけど
I still screw up sometimes.
たまに やっちゃったりして
I thought it'd be best if no one knew who I was, so I tried to avoid standing out,
だったら 目立たないようにしようと思って
影薄くしてたんだけど
but Kanna talked to me,
そんな私に
柑菜が 声かけてきてくれて
and then Tetsuro and Kirishima became my friends too...
哲郎君や 霧島君も 友達になってくれて
I was so happy, and I had so much fun with them.
すごく 嬉しくて 楽しくて
That's why I didn't want them to find out.
だから 知られてたくなくて
I'm not a pervert...
私 変態なんかじゃ
You're just stupid.
お前 バカじゃねえの
If it happens so often, just keep spares in your bag.
よく忘れるんなら
変えのやつ かばんに入れときゃいいだろう
I-I guess...
そ そう
Just tell people you're going to the bathroom and put them on.
そんで トイレでも行く振りして入ってくりゃいいじゃん
You carry around your PE clothes, don't you?
体操着だってあるだろう
But...
そうなんだ
Getting all worked up isn't going to solve anything.
焦ってあたふたしたって物事解決しねえんだよ
You didn't want anyone to know who you were?
何が影薄くだ
You're way too cynical.
ネガティブ思考すぎるっての
But...
困ってんなら 相談しろ
You should've told us if you had a problem.
We would've helped you.
フォローするに決まってんだろう
Kanna and Kai... and me, too.
柑菜も 海も 俺も
But...
でも
No buts.
でもじゃねえよ
But what if everyone hated me because of that...
皆に嫌われたらって
We could never hate you.
しねえよ
Really?
ホントに
Can't you trust us?
俺らが信用できねえのかよ
Just tell me what's on your mind.
だからさ 言いたいこと言えよ な
I like you.
好き
Tetsuro,
哲郎君が 好き
I like you.
I love you.
大好き
I see.
そうですか
樹下 そんなことあったんだ
So that's what happened with Kinoshita.
That's why she was so...
だから あんなに
She said she was sorry.
ごめんなさいって言ってた
ああ 情けない
I'm so pathetic.
I knew she was forcing herself, but I didn't really try to talk to her about it.
あいつが無理してるの 気づいてたのに
ちゃんと 聞いてやれなくて
You ended up taking care of it.
先輩に 任せる形になっちゃって
I think she wanted to tell you.
樹下さんは海人君に言おうとしてたと思う
But I ended up telling her I wanted to talk first.
でも その前に 私が呼び出しちゃったから
You mean Kinoshita?
樹下を
Why?
用事でもあったんですか
ああ だから 昼の時 来たんですね
Oh. So that's why you found us this afternoon.
Was there something you needed to tell her?
何が言うことでもあったんですか
Well...
そ それは
I...
それは
That's beautiful.
綺麗ですね
They got along so well!
なんかね 二人いい感じで
あたし お邪魔みたいな感じで
I felt like I was just getting in the way!
哲郎さん好きな子いないって言ってたのに
Tetsuro said he didn't have someone he liked!
I just made a fool of myself!
私どんだけピエロだな
You came with me on this trip so I could escape my heartbreak,
私の傷心旅行に付き合ってくれたのに
and now the same thing happened to you.
同じになっちゃったね
It's not fair! She was actually kind of dumb too!
本物の天然 ずるいよ
Too bad.
参っちゃうな この夏 二度目だよ
That's the second time this summer.
It's gotten late.
遅くなっちゃったね
Yeah.
そうだな
Do you think they're worried?
心配してるかな
Yeah.
そうだな
さっきの返事とか いいから
You don't have to tell me how you feel.
I already know.
分かってるから
I wonder how Ishigaki is doing.
石垣君 どうしてるかしら
今も 樹下の連れの子に
He's probably still being chased around by Kinoshita's friend.
追い回されてたりして
I guess guys can get put off by girls who come on too strong, huh?
やっぱり 女の子にあれだけアプローチされたら
男の子は悪い気しない
I guess so.
まあ それは 多少が
Was it the same with Kinoshita?
樹下さんの時も
Don't tease me.
いじめないでくださいよ
Sorry, sorry.
ごめん ごめん
Hey...
先輩
What is it?
何
I don't want to be chased by someone.
俺 追いかけられるんじゃなくて
I want to be the one chasing.
追いかけていたいんです
I want to chase after
好きな人のことを
追いかけたい
the girl I like.
But if my feelings are going to make you uncomfortable...
でも
俺の気持ちが 先輩を困らせるようなら
They won't!
そんなことない
I'm not uncomfortable at all.
困ってなんか
ないよ
ダっ ダメ
Don't...
What are you doing meow?
何してるにゃ
Ta-Ta-Ta-Tanigawa?!
たたたた 谷川さん
We weren't doing anything. Wait, why are you wearing that?
いや これはなんでもなくて
つうか 何 その 格好
Where were you two until just meow?
二人っきりで どこ行ってたんなにゃ
Wait, wait... Where the hell were you?!
つうか どこ行ってたんですか
What's going on here?
ちょ 何なんです これ
Girl's night. Just the two of us.
二人っきりの女子会をしていたのよ
Tanigawa, are you all right?
谷川さん 大丈夫
Takatsuki!
はあ 貴月先輩
What are you doing, Tanigawa?
な 何してんだよ 谷川
Now's your turn, Kaito!
じゃあ 海人君
Stop it!
ダメ
Hey, stop it!
やめろ
Kanna?
柑菜は
What are you doing?
何やってんだ
Tetsu-meow and Meow!
哲郎にゃんに 美桜にゃんにゃ
Where were you two, meow?
二人でどこ行ってた にゃにゃ
Meow?
つうか
Well? Where the hell were you two?!
どこ行ってたのにゃ
What?
何なんだ
Kanna!
か 柑菜
Don't just leave me here! That's not fair!
ずるい ずるい
私だけ のけもので
And I'm tired.
それで 眠い
You can't sleep out here!
ダ ダメだよ こんなとこで寝ちゃう
What's going on?!
何なんだよ これは
Meow!
にゃん
あなた
You... protected me.
私をかばって
I'm so sorry!
ごめんなさい
ありがとう
But thank you.
Cut.
カット
Now that Kinoshita has finished all of her scenes, we're done filming.
これで 樹下さんのパートは終わり 撮了です
Good work.
お疲れ様
You too.
こちらこそ
Anyway, I gotta catch my plane.
じゃあ 私 飛行機の時間あるんで ここで
Sorry for keeping you here.
悪いな ぎりぎりまで粘って
No worries. Good luck with the movie!
平気平気
撮影頑張って
Send me a copy when you're done.
出来上がったら 絶対見せてね
Sure.
Here, Kinoshita.
樹下さん これ
あ ありがとうございます
Thanks.
Seaboy will be gone if you don't act.
ぼやぼやしてると 海ちゃん 取っちゃいますよ
See ya!
じゃあ
Gonna miss her?
寂しい
Maybe a little.
まあ 少しは
She was your first love, after all.
初恋の人ですもんね
I told you she wasn't!
違いますって
Our flight leaves in the evening?
俺ら 夕方の便だっけ
It's at 5 o'clock.
１７時のだよ
We're done filming for today.
今日の撮影は終了
As soon as we clean up the set,
撤収の準備ができ次第
let's enjoy the Okinawan ocean.
沖縄の海を楽しみましょう
Hell yeah!
賛成
Heads up!
先輩
I realized...
私 気づいてしまったの
I looked for the reason why I fell in love
and tried solemn words
how I...
私
feel about Kaito.
海人君が
Once I realized my feelings,
the threads had gotten hopelessly tangled up
If I'd been able to say it
without hesitation
you wouldn't have to cry now
We paint a picture of feelings that pierce the clouds
Forever we will remember the scent of summer on the wind
My memories of when I was with someone
put color into my life, drop by drop, like the evening rain
You are in trouble.
Episode Eight
Kitahara! Lemon suggested we all go to the festival.
北原さん 檸檬が皆でお祭りに行こうって
That's dangerous!
それは危険です
Why?
どうして
I smell a conspiracy!
陰謀の匂いがします